hey everyone I'm Brian I'm excited to be
joining you all at mux on the pipe from
engineering team a little bit about me I
grew up in New Jersey until I went off
to college at Virginia Tech go Hokies uh
and after college I moved to Northern
Virginia which is right outside DC I've
worked at various companies and kind of
found my Niche really loving building
reliable systems that are distributed
and have really unique problems that I
feel like I can help solve and and I
really love making the developer
experience and running on those
platforms as enjoyable as possible
and so that's kind of how I found myself
in platform engineering before joining
mux I was part of the platform teams at
Gannett as well as New Relic and along
the way uh I adopted My adorable rescue
dog tag who knows how much he is the
center of my attention uh in my spare
time I love growing and taking care of
my plants the more exotic or spicy
pepper they are the better
and as well as skiing I wish I could do
that more now but I really missed that
when I was living in New Jersey my
question to you all is do you think a
taco is a sandwich
why are